export default data = [
    {
        question: "CARTON, ENJOYMENT, WORDSMITH Which of the following words continues the above sequence?",
        options: ["COPY","REEF","COPE","REST"],
        correct_option: "REEF"
    },
    {
        question: "What number comes next in this sequence? 25, 32, 27, 36, ?",
        options: ["27","46","29"],
        correct_option: "27"
    },
    {
        question: "Which word means the same as ANCHORITE?",
        options: ["recluse","hieroglyphics","trammel","lackey"],
        correct_option: "recluse"
    },
    {
        question: "Mary is 16 years old. She is 4 times older than her brother. How old will Mary be when she is twice his age?",
        options: ["20","24","28","25"],
        correct_option: "24"
    },
    {
        question: " A car travels at a speed of 40 mph over a certain distance and then returns over the same distance at a speed of 60 mph. What is the average speed for the total journey?",
        options: ["30 mph","40 mph ","60 mph ","48 mph"],
        correct_option: "48 mph"
    },
    {
        question: "SUNDAY, MONDAY, WEDNESDAY, SATURDAY, WEDNESDAY Which day comes next?",
        options: ["SUNDAY ","MONDAY","WEDNESDAY ","SATURDAY"],
        correct_option: "MONDAY"
    },
    {
        question: " Which is the odd one out?",
        options: ["SALIFEROUS","EVACUATION","EXHAUSTION","INOCULATED"],
        correct_option: "EVACUATION"
    },
    {
        question: "A, B, D, G, K. Which letter comes next in the sequence?",
        options: ["N","P","M","Q"],
        correct_option: "P"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the five is least like the other four?",
        options: ["Eel","Shark","Dolphin","Turtle"],
        correct_option: "Turtle"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the only flying mammal?",
        options: ["The bat","The flying squirrel","The bald eagle","The colugo"],
        correct_option: "The bat"
    }
]